一份牛排三明治
One steak sandwich
一个门斯特起司汉堡
and a cheeseburger with muenster cheese.
没有门斯特起司
We're out of muenster.
什么时候没的
Oh, since when?
我想想  从1982年开店至今
Well, let's see, the diner opened in '82.
就没有过
So '82.
抱歉  我们没有门斯特起司
Hi, sorry but we're out of muenster.
你不是吧  兄台
Seriously, dude?
我就想吃门斯特起司
I wanted muenster.
抱歉  不过我们有切达  瑞士  跟美国起司
Sorry, we have cheddar, Swiss or American.
我讨厌切达
I hate cheddar
瑞士起司也烂爆了
and Swiss blows.
那美国起司呢
Well... then American?
美国起司啊
American cheese?
你当我是小学生吃早点啊
What am I, at grade school?
熊孩子  快滚去校长办公室
Yeah, go to the principal's office.
老娘现在没心情招呼白痴
I can't have another idiot up my ass right now.
我要忙死了
It's at capacity.
麦克斯  我来处理
Max, I got this.
您要再看一遍菜单吗
Would you like to see the menu again?
什么狗屁菜单  我就要门斯特起司
This is crap, okay, I wanted muenster.
我还想当财富500强公司的老板呢
Well, I wanted to be running a Fortune 500 company
你当老娘想服务你这种幼稚男啊
instead of waiting on a toxic man-child like yourself.
无奈愿望很美好  现实很残酷
But, we can't always get what we want.
所以给老娘乖乖点别的  塞进你的狗嘴
So, order something else, put it in your pie hole
然后继续你悲催的人生
and get on with your damn life.
欢迎进入服务生界
Welcome to waitress.
我们等你加入好久了
We've been expecting you.
给  厄尔  10号桌结账
Here you go, table ten, Earl.
明天有何绝妙计划
Have any exciting plans for tomorrow?
别在睡梦中上天堂  我就阿弥陀佛了
Just trying to not die in my sleep, Max.
你呢
How about you?
我要去探望卡洛琳的马
I'm going to visit Caroline's horse.
一个白人富婆收养了他
He was adopted by a rich white lady
还给他所有我们给不起的东西
who could give him everything we couldn't afford to.
基本上就是一切事物
Which is everything.
白人还真是什么都领养呀
White people will adopt anything.
我计划好去见栗宝的最佳路线了
I figured out the best way to go see Chestnut.
先搭J号火车到4号线
We take the J train to the 4,
再由4号线转中央车站
the 4 to Grand Central,
然后转火车去河谷站
change trains to Riverdale
最后下车走3个街区  就到他华丽的新家了
and walk three blocks to his fancy new stable.
好像要漂洋过海哦  需要"打"旅游疫苗吗
Sounds exotic. Do I need a travel shot?
不必  不过中央车站有段地下道挺乱的
No, but there's a dicey underpass at Grand Central
在那倒有可能被开枪"打"
where we might get shot.
要去见我的小宝贝  好激动啊
I am so excited to see my baby again.
我也是
Me too.
如果是生活台的剧  那剧情就是
In the Lifetime movie version,
我们到那里发现栗宝更喜欢他的新家
we get there and Chestnut likes his new home better
然后我们抱头痛哭
and then we cry.
抱歉  你们好
Excuse me, Hi.
抱歉打扰了
Sorry to bother you.
我叫蕾雅  我有个难言之隐
I'm Rhya, I'm a little embarrassed.
我突然月事来潮
I just got my period.
恭喜恭喜[希伯来语]
Mazel tov.
你们俩有人带了卫生棉条吗
Do either of you have a tampon?
我没有
Not me.
我一般都是跑进森林里  等大姨妈走了再出来
I just go off Into the Woods and don't come out until it's over.
我有带
I have one.
真抱歉  麻烦你们了
I'm so sorry to bother you guys.
小意思  "卫生棉条的夏天"嘛
No problem, "Sisterhood of the Traveling Panty Shields"
抱歉  我好像没带
Actually, no, I don't have one.
这里有25分
Here's a quarter,
-在女厕所里有个棉条贩卖机  -谢谢了
-there's a tampon machine in the ladies' room. - Thanks.
6号桌  上菜
Pick up, table six.
我"不小心"听到你们的对话
I couldn't help overhear.
我有棉条呢
I have tampon.
奥列格  你怎么会有棉条
Oleg, why do you have a tampon?
就跟我不抽烟也随身带打火机一样
Same reason I carry a lighter, even though I don't smoke.
当英雄感觉很好很强大
Feels good to be the hero.
抱歉  又来打扰了  能再要点零钱吗
Sorry, again, but do you have any more change?
-一个要75分  -只要25分吧
- It's 75 cents. - It's a quarter.
是75分  贩卖机上写着呢
75. Says so on the machine.
最好不是  否则我要打爆这破机子
It better not or I'm about to rage against the machine.
我靠
What?
阿憨  进来  我有话跟你说
Han, I need to see you in here now.
可那是女厕所呀
But that is the ladies' room.
怕啥
You're fine.
很多女人经常会带小孩进来
Women bring their little boys in here all the time.
大家都穿戴整齐了吗
Everybody decent?
有男人进女厕啦
Man in the ladies' room.
我对我的无礼闯入感到抱歉
I apologize for personal intrusion.
你遮眼睛干嘛
You don't have to cover your eyes.
进女厕而已  又不是看日蚀
It's a ladies' room, not a solar eclipse.
麦克斯  你为什么要挑一个
Max, why do you want to see me
这么不恰当的会面场地见我呀
in this inappropriate meeting place?
原因在这里  棉条贩卖机
This is why. The tampon machine.
哎呀  这不是男人该讨论的话题
Oh, this is not man topic.
我不想跟你讨论你们女人
I do not wish to discuss time of the month
每个月都有几天得追逐"棉老鼠"的事
when ladies must chase the cotton mouse.
追逐棉老鼠
Chase the cotton mouse?
天啊  你两性教育课去哪上的
Geeze, where'd you get your sex education?
儿童电视剧吗
Lambchop's playalong?
阿憨  棉条价钱是你涨的吗
Han, you changed the price of tampons?
是的  但是谈这个不合适吧
Yes, this is not appropriate talk.
错  是你这么做不合适吧
No, this is not appropriate action.
人家卖25分都卖了几百年了
They've been a quarter forever.
看到这机器多旧了没啊
Look how old this machine is.
哈莉特·塔布曼都在这机子买过呢
Harriet Tubman used to get her tampons here.
我是个男商人
I'm a businessman.
我要强调是"男"字
Emphasis on the man.
我不该进来的
I do not belong in here.
喂  喂
Hey, hey!
别逼老娘追你  你这小卡其裤鼠
Don't make me chase you, you little khaki mouse.
阿憨  众所皆知  人们在紧急情况下
Look, Han, everyone knows there are certain things
需要的某些东西
that people need in an emergency
是完全不应该涨价的
that you never raise the price on.
比如什么
Things like what?
我现在想到的就有
Off the top of my head,
卫生棉条和超大瓶啤酒
tampons and 40-ounce beers.
麦克斯  你干嘛这么不爽啊
Max, why are you so upset?
不过就是涨了50分钱嘛
It is only two more quarters.
阿憨  你这相当于提价了两倍
Han, that's a 200% price hike.
太黑心了
That's outrageous.
你这是在占女人的便宜
You're taking advantage of women.
如果是男人来月经
If men were the ones who got periods,
那棉条会跟狂欢节的彩珠一样
tampons would be thrown free from floats
从花车上免费扔下来
like Mardi Gras beads.
我也曾去过狂欢节  当时我11岁
I went to Mardi Gras once-- I was 11.
我妈跟她的新男友想去玩
My mom and her new boyfriend wanted to go,
他们需要个不喝酒的驾驶员
and they needed a designated driver.
厄尔  我需要男人的意见
Earl, I need a man's opinion.
餐厅的一切产品
Is it my right to raise the price
我是不是都有权涨价
of any product in my diner?
比如什么产品
What product are we talking about?
卫生棉条
Tampons.
天啊  小兄弟
Oh, brother.
深吸一口气  就此罢手吧
Uh, you gotta just relax and butt out.
相信我
Trust me.
多年以前  我也碰过这种情况
I been in this situation a long time.
还记得佛罗[流量]阿姨吧
Remember Aunt Flo?
那是我亲姨呢
That was my aunt.
阿憨  虽然你有商机可以趁机捞一笔
Han, just because you can take advantage of a business situation,
但也不能趁火打劫呀
doesn't mean you should.
这是供求法则
It is law of supply and demand.
那我要求[需求]你改回原价
Fine, then I demand you roll back the price on the supply.
阿憨  别在这种时候当1%的人啊
Come on Han, don't be so 1% about it.
你觉得99%党占领华尔街那事严重吗
You think occupy Wall Street was a big deal?
"占领卫生棉"可是有过之无不及哦
Wait till you see occupy tampon.
女人虽然每个月只抗议一次
We only protest once a month,
可一抗议  就是群情激昂的五到七天哦
but it's an intense five to seven days.
搞定  找到牛奶了
Got it. Found the milk.
速度比找黄油快多了
And I found it even faster than the butter.
商品又没有跟你玩躲猫猫
You know they're not hiding it from you.
我们是来超市购物  不是玩寻宝游戏
It's a grocery store, not a sorority scavenger hunt.
超市购物好有趣啊
Grocery shopping is so fun.
我小时候总是好奇
When I was little, I always wondered
这些吃的都是哪来的
where this stuff came from.
那是什么啊
What's that?
要寄给我妈的生日卡
Birthday card for my mom.
我看看
Aww, let me see.
怎么写着"早日康复"啊
"Get better soon"?
你不是说是生日贺卡吗
I thought you said it was a birthday card.
是啊  只有这张感觉比较符合
It is, that's the only one that seemed
我跟她的关系
appropriate for our relationship.
你真的希望你妈生日
Do you really want your mom to get
收到一张探病慰问卡吗
a get well card on her birthday?
好吧  那这张有草莓的总可以了吧
Okay... here's one with a strawberry, that's fine.
反正她在乎的也只是卡里面夹的50块
It's really about the 50 bucks inside anyway.
听得我好伤感啊
That makes me sad.
伤感啊  我帮你
Sad? I can fix that.
吃个糖吧  吃完心情立马好
Have a treat, it'll perk you right back up.
麦克斯  你把人家的糖果包扎烂了
Max, you just stabbed a bag of candy.
不用怕  人家只会以为是
That's okay, they'll just think
是黑帮路过是干的
a gang came through and did it.
捅糖帮吗
A candy gang?
成员是一群酸甜娃糖吗
What, like the sour patch kids?
袖手旁观  视而不见就行了
Just step away and pretend you didn't do it.
你不都这样吗
That's what you do.
再买十盒
We just need to grab ten boxes
邓肯海恩牌的蛋糕粉就行了
of Duncan Hines cake mix and we're done.
我们要蛋糕粉干嘛
Why would we need to do that?
你说呢  当然是做小蛋糕啊
Why do you think? To make the cupcakes.
我以为小蛋糕是你自制的呢
I thought the cupcakes were homemade.
是啊  在"自"家现"制"呀
They are, I make them in my home.
原来你都是用蛋糕粉做的啊
You've been using a boxed cake mix?
别大惊小怪的  我累的时候才这么干
Relax, I only use it when I'm tired.
而且我还是会加入我的秘方
And I add a secret ingredient of my own to the mix
让蛋糕美味无法挡
that makes them irresistible.
你原料都用现成的  不会觉得羞耻吗
So you have no shame using the store-bought mix?
羞耻在我眼中是浮云
I've no shame about anything.
那玩意儿就跟科莎一样被捧过头了
Shame is overrated like Ke$ha.
其实  她应该改艺名叫"科耻"
In fact, they should rename shame "Keshame"
我刚买了科莎的专辑  太"科耻"了
I just bought a Ke$ha album, I'm so keshamed.
怎么没有人帮我们装袋啊
Shouldn't there be someone to do this for us?
他可能在刚那里
Oh, he's probably in the aisle
清理捅糖帮过境后的残局吧
cleaning up after the candy gang.
我们这里才没有捅糖帮
There was no candy gang in here tonight.
只是有个坏心眼的顾客  不是咩
That was a sneaky customer, now wasn't it?
瞧
Hey, look.
买给栗宝的  好想见他哦
For Chestnut, I can't wait.
我专门买了带叶的  跟兔八哥爱吃的一样
I got him the kind with tops on them, like Bugs Bunny.
明天他见到我们一定会很开心的
He'll be so excited when he sees the two of us tomorrow.
我知道
I know.
我是说见到我跟胡萝卜开心
I was talking about me and the carrots.
好了  总计70块49分
All right now, your total is $70.49.
哇  好贵啊
Wow, that seems like a lot.
价钱又不是我定的  有问题咩
I don't make the prices, now do I?
没有  我就发表下看法
No, I was just commenting.
这又不是新闻台  要这么多看法咩
Well, it's not CNN now, is it?
-给  把折价券给她  -折价券啊
- Here, give her the coupons. - The coupons?
对啊  拿去
Yeah, here.
麦克斯  你居然用折价券
Max, you use coupons?
我真心没想到啊
I had no idea.
你居然用那种看《猎捕恋童癖》上的变态的眼神看我
You're looking at me like I'm on To Catch a Predator.
我们人穷志不能穷  用我的小费结吧
We don't need to use those, I have my tip money right here.
说什么傻话  我有折价券呢
What are you talking about, I have coupons.
给  快拿去啊
Here, take them.
我有...
I-I have--
我做不到  也不想做到
I can't, I don't want to.
我已经够堕落了  不能变得无下限
I've fallen so far, I can't fall any further.
拜托别逼我
Don't make me.
没必要因为折价券而觉得"科耻"
There's no need to go down a keshame spiral.
您好  她有折价券
Hi, she has coupons.
哎哟  现在才说你有折价券啊
Oh, now you tell me you have coupons?
早该跟我说了  不是咩
Should have told me before, now shouldn't ya?
我真心不想跟你说的  是她逼我的
I didn't wanna tell you at all, she made me.
不是咩
Now didn't ya?
干嘛啊  没什么大不了的
Look, it's not a big deal.
很多人都用折价券啊
Lots of people use coupons.
折价券是给...
Coupons are for--
穷人用的  没错
Poor people, yes.
我们就是穷人
Like us.
穷人才会站在收银台前说
People who stand at the cash register and say things like,
"哇  要七十块  好贵啊"
"Wow, $70? That seems like a lot."
现在总计  12块7毛
Your new total is $12.70
等等  一下子价钱就能从70块变12块吗
Wait, it just went from $70 to $12?
不费吹灰之力
Just like that?
一样的商品  更优惠的价钱
The same food for less money?
真的完全一样的商品吗
The exact same food?
怎么可能有这么好的事啊
How is that even possible?
你用了折价券啊  不是咩
You used coupons, now didn't ya.
麦克斯  折价券太神了
Max, coupons are genius.
我迟到了  我知道
I'm late, I know.
我刚接到栗宝的短信
I just got a text from Chestnut.
他问  "你们在哪呢"
"Where are you?
"我穿着最好的西装恭候大驾呢"
I'm wearing my best suit."
他把西装打成"四"装
He spelled suit with a four,
不过马蹄打字  情有可原
but that's pretty good for a horse.
我有正当理由
I have a good reason.
15个鸡肉饼
15 chicken pot pies.
原价1块47分
Regular price: $1.47.
折价后  免费
Coupon price: Free!
因为我买了15个  用双倍折价券正好免费
'Cause I bought 15 and used the double coupon in-store sale combo.
瞧我折价界行话说的多溜啊
Listen to me with the lingo already.
让我想起去华尔街实习的第一天
Reminds me of my first day interning on Wall Street.
鸡肉饼
Chicken pot pies?
你自己都不爱吃
You don't even like them.
我爱不爱吃又如何
What does it matter if I like them or not?
反正是免费的
They were free.
不要钱啊
It's free money.
谁不喜欢天上掉馅饼的好事
Who doesn't like free money?
天上有没有掉馅饼我不知道
I don't know about free money,
我只知道某人看起来像
but this is like watching someone
第一次尝到毒品甜头似的
free base for the first time.
栗宝没事的
Chestnut's fine.
晚个一天又不会怎么样
It's not a big deal.
哎哟  栗宝又给我发来一条短信
Ooh, oh, I just got another text from Chestnut.
"我好孤单哦  唯有以烟慰籍"
"I'm so lonely, I just tried smoking."
我们可以明天去看他嘛
We can go tomorrow.
如果这是生活台的剧
In the Lifetime movie version,
那剧情就是  我们错过法庭指定的日子
we just missed the day we were appointed by the court,
现在栗宝要被新爸妈带去别城市了
and Chestnut's new parents move him out of town.
然后我们泪洒当场
And we cry.
我明白  只是昨晚尝过甜头后
I get it, it's just that after last night,
我就对折价券的好念念不忘  连醒来都想着
I woke up fascinated by the concept of coupons.
所以我上网搜了下
So I did some research.
搜到网上有名奇女子
I found this woman online
自封为"威廉斯堡折价券女皇"
who calls herself the Williamsburg Coupon Queen.
只不过她念成折"家"券
Only she calls them "Cue-pons."
难道那样才是正确的念法吗
Is that the correct way to pronounce it?
算了  我也那样念吧
Eh, I'm gonna go with her way
毕竟人家才是女皇嘛
after all, she is the queen.
罐装南瓜
Canned pumpkin?
10罐  双倍折扣后  5分钱一罐
Ten cans, double coupon, five cents each.
太好了  我一直有个晚上躺床上
Great, 'cause I'm always lying in bed at night
想着要能开一罐南瓜会有多爽的梦呢
thinking I wish I could crack open a can of pumpkin.
我找到了个折"家"券  你可以送给你妈
Oh, and I found a coupon for you to send your mom
一个可自选的花篮当生日礼物
an edible arrangement for her birthday.
一朵凤梨雕的雏菊比贺卡夹现金有意义多了
A pretty pineapple daisy says so much more than cash in a card.
而且能打六折呢
And it's for 40% off the regular price.
太巧了  我妈也是个六折妈
That's perfect because my mom was 40% off a regular mom.
麦克斯  袋子里还有要给你的小礼物哦
And Max, I do have something else for you in this bag.
你见了包准欣喜若狂哟
Somet'hing that'll make you very happy.
开腻南瓜罐后  换口味的地瓜罐吗
Canned yams for when I get tired of canned pumpkin?
比那个还棒  你瞧
Better, look.
接招吧  李憨
Look out, Han Lee.
老娘要"棉"起抗战啦
I'm about to get my tamp on.
唉 居然有人穿小男孩的低领毛衣
Well well, if it isn't everything that's wrong with the current economy,
世界经济的萧条可见一斑呀
in a boys' v-neck sweater.
哎呀  你这是在干嘛呢
Oh, what do you think you are doing?
把吸管放进罐子里啊
Oh, just putting straws in the container...
以防...
in case, uh...
以防有女士突然需要个吸管
Just in case a woman might suddenly need a straw
又碰巧没有75分钱
and not have 75 cents.
那些不是吸管
Those are not straws.
它们不应该出现在公共场合
They do not belong in public.
你母亲难道没教你
Didn't your mother ever teach you
那是女性不能说的秘密吗
that is secret, no-no private lady thing?
你连那个词都不敢说
You can't even say the name.
说啊  满口钱的华尔街男孩
Come on Wall Street, if you can sell it,
你敢涨价  就要敢说出口啊
you should be able to bring yourself to say it.
打死我也不说那词
I will never speak of it.
就说啊  棉条  棉条  棉条
Just say it. Tampon, tampon, tampon.
有那么难吗
What's the big deal?
我们乌克兰还有以此为题的流行歌呢
In Ukraine, there are pop songs about it.
*  她好美丽  她好有个性  *
*  She's so pretty, she's so grouchy.  *
吧台上不应该放这种东西
That is inappropriate counter display.
收回去
You take it down.
你把涨的价收回去  我就照办
You take down the price and I will.
不要  这是自由的市场
No, it is free market.
价格多少  我说了算
I charge what I want.
我可是老板
I am the boss.
麦克斯  有人落下了一叠满是折"家"券的报纸
Max, someone left a stack of newspapers filled with cue-pons,
你瞧  邓肯蛋糕粉双倍折价呢
and look, a double for Duncan Hines.
今天还能更完美点吗
Could this day get any better?
对了  第4  7  8号桌  要结账
Oh, and tables four, seven and eight want their checks.
好的
Okay.
随时准备出击
Have 'em ready right here.
麦克斯  不行  那是私密物品
Max, no, that is private!
您的账单
Here's your check.
附赠一点小礼物
And a little something extra,
赠给没有随身携带75分钱的女士们
compliments of women without three quarters everywhere.
感谢您的莅临
Thank you very much.
我不知道您的流量
I don't know about your flow,
所以我给了您普通型  跟大流量型
so I gave you a regular and a super.
麦克斯  你有没有羞耻心啊
Max, have you no shame?
没有
Nope.
女士们  每个月姨妈到访时
Ladies, at that time of the month,
我请你们想想这男人
I invite you to think of this man.
就这男人  李憨  那边那位
This man, Han Lee, right over here.
就是这男的决定  让大家月事变"贵"事
The man who thinks your menses should be more expenses.
好了  好了  我会把价钱还原
Okay, okay, I will lower the price
降回25分钱
back to a quarter.
此话题结束  画下句点[月经]
And that is end of discussion, period.
哎哟
Oh.
棉条赠贵宾
Tampons for everyone.
麦克斯  你简直就是女性卫生界的诺玛蕾啊
Max, you are the Norma Rae of feminine hygiene.
今天风真大
It's so windy.
折价券采购又大过去见你儿子了吗
Choosing coupon shopping over going to see your son again?
真是"科耻"啊
That's a keshame.
如果这是生活台的剧
In the Lifetime movie version,
剧情便是  你这个不称职的母亲被带走了
this is where they take you away as an unfit mother.
然后我完全无动于衷
And I don't cry.
对不起嘛  可我看到
I'm sorry, but I just saw
这些蛋糕粉折"家"券今天到期
that all these cake mix cue-pons expire today.
我很快就搞定
I'll be real quick.
进去出来  只要10分钟
Ten minutes, in and out.
每次有男的这么说  我能拿折"家"券的话...
If I had a cue-pon for every time I heard that from a guy.
给  翻翻这报纸
Here, start going through these papers
找找里面送的双倍蛋糕粉折"家"券
and look for the cake mix double cue-pon.
如果用双倍折价再加上店内返现
If I combine these with the in-store bonus,
我们不止能用超低折"家"价买下蛋糕粉
not only will we get the lower cue-pon mix price,
还能拿到23块的现金返现呢
but they will actually give us $23 back!
我愿意给你24块钱  拜托别再说折"家"券
I'll give you $24 to stop saying cue-pon.
来吧  从这堆报纸里整理出折"家"券吧
Come on, start pulling out the ones for the cake mix.
就跟秋风扫落叶般容易
It'll be a breeze.
这才叫秋风扫落叶
No, that was a breeze.
我的宝贝折"家"券啊
My cue-pons!
你不在乎头发乱了  只在乎你的折价券
The fact that you're more worried about your coupons
你的堕落程度可见一斑呀
than your hair shows how far you've fallen.
我的天啊  真不敢相信
Oh, my God, I can't believe it.
麦克斯  她就是"威廉斯堡折"家"券女皇"
Max, it's the Williamsburg Cue-pon Queen.
她的后冠放哪了  手推车里吗
Where'd she leave her crown, in the minivan?
太兴奋了  我要去致上我的敬意
This is so exciting. I have to go pay my respects.
我们可没时间
We don't have time for this.
快把蛋糕粉扔进手推车
Just throw the cake mix into the cart
否则就赶不上火车了
or we'll miss the train.
给  淡定  吃颗糖吧
There, calm down, have a treat.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
打扰您了  女皇殿下
Excuse me, your highness,
您就是折"家"券女皇本尊吧
but aren't you the cue-pon queen?
我是卡洛琳
I'm Caroline.
我是弗雷迪  我现在没空闲聊
Freddie, and I can't talk right now
因为如果我失去我的地位
because if I lose my place--
-您会疯掉的  -我会疯...掉...的
- you'll lose your mind! - I'm gonna lose... my... mind...
我知道  您在节目上说过
I know. You say that on your show.
我不会打扰您的  可如果我告诉您
I won't bother you, but I think you'll be excited
我折价生涯才开始第二天  我就已经学会
when I tell you that it's only my second day
如何利用买蛋糕粉挣钱了  您一定倍感欣慰
and I already learned how to make money on the purchase of cake mix.
我只需买够40盒  就可以拿到...
All I have to do is buy 40 boxes and we get the--
商店返现  没错
Store bonus, yeah.
蛋糕粉  这种折"家"不常有啊
Cake mix... That's a rare cue-pon.
你怎么发现的
Where'd you find it?
昨天的传单啊
Yesterday's circulars.
你没看见吗
Didn't you see it?
我错过了
I missed it.
去车上把那堆传单拿来
Go to the truck and get the stockpile of circulars.
瞧他跑得多快
Look at him go.
你居然大肆扫货
You're sweeping the shelves.
你在节目上说  大肆扫货是犯规的
On your show, you said sweeping the shelves was out of line.
麦克斯
Max!
这些是我的  我先来的
These are mine, I was here first.
我觉得奋战到最后的肯定是她
I think she's probably gonna be here last,
走吧  我们不需要这些
so let's go, we don't need these.
就要  如果我们不拿够40盒
We do, if we don't get 40 boxes,
这些就不能免费
they won't be free.
我见过真正的女皇  你一点女皇范都没有
I've met actual queens and this isn't royal behavior.
麦克斯  她刚刚推我了
Max, she just body-checked me.
再推我  我就去美国大使馆举报你
Push me again and I will report you to the American embassy.
麦克斯  过来
Max, get in here.
想找茬是吧
Oh, we got a problem?
要找茬来啊
Oh, we got a problem.
去死吧
Oh, hell no!
怎么办
What do we do?
袖手旁观  装不知情就行了
You step away and pretend you didn't do it.
就像这样
That's what you do.
24  25
24, 25--
你就是故意让我等  不是咩
You're making me wait, now aren't ya?
等我数到40就好了
Just till I get to 40.
26  27  28
26, 27, 28.
拜托  我买给你好了
Come on, I'll buy it for you.
对啊  成全那个傻帽吧
Come on, take up the bitch on his offer
咱们快去看栗宝吧
and let's go see Chestnut.
麦克斯  闭嘴  我数数呢
Max, shh, I'm counting.
如果我们的蛋糕粉跟折价券的比例不对
If we don't have the exact right mix-to-coupon ratio
就那不到免费的钱了
we won't get our free money.
好了  我刚数到哪里了
Okay, where was I?
真业余
Amateur.
你专业  女皇殿下
Real mature, your highness.
我们还有地方要去呢
We have places to go.
好了  40
Okay, 40.
结吧  塔尼娅
Take it away, Tanya.
慢着  这是什么
Wait, what is this?
这不是邓肯海恩的  这是贝氏堡的
This isn't Duncan Hines, it's Pillsbury.
打哪儿冒出来的
Where did this come from?
我放进去的
I put it in.
你不能这么做
You can't do that.
必须全部都是邓肯海恩的
It has to be all Duncan Hines.
我要用贝氏堡的
I needed Pillsbury.
不行
Well, you can't have it.
-我要用  -为什么
- I need it! - Why?
-我要用  -为什么要用
因为秘方就是它
That's the secret ingredient.
我放一勺贝氏堡
I throw a spoon of Pillsbury
进邓肯海恩里
in the Duncan Hines.
贝氏堡
Pillsbury?
是它成就了你
That's what makes it you?
是它成就了美味可口的小蛋糕
That's what makes it more delicious.
塔尼娅  停下  有人犯规
Tanya, stop, flag on the play.
给  把这个放回去  拿过别个来
Here, take this back and get me another.
趁我还有时间  我要去看栗宝了
You know what, I'm just gonna go see Chestnut while I still have time.
别  麦克斯  拜托换一个回来嘛
No, Max, please take this back and get me another one.
是你自己要用
You're the one who wanted to use
超市的蛋糕粉  而不是一开始就自制原料
the store-bought mix instead of making your own from scratch.
所以回去给我换一盒吧
So go back and get me another mix.
我之所以用超市的  是因为我做不出自制
I used the mix because I don't know how to make my own.
没人教我
No one ever taught me.
没人教我烘培
No one taught me how to bake.
没人教我用卫生棉条
No one taught me how to use tampons.
没人教我任何事
No one taught me anything.
你还觉得我应该送份好点的礼物给我妈吗
You still think I should send my mom a better gift?
我猜也没人教你怎么结账吧
And no one taught you how to check out, either.
我要走了
I'm going.
麦克斯
Max.
你得去换一盒蛋糕粉  不是咩
You need to get another mix, now don't ya?
我马上就去  很快回来
I'll go get it, won't take a minute.
高下立见了吧
Who's the queen now?
嘿  伙计
Hey, my dude.
瞧你珠圆玉润  锦衣华服
Look at you and your fancy coat.
退休生活过得挺滋润啊
Retirement looks good on you.
说过会来看你
Told you I'd come by to see you.
给你带了爱吃的胡萝卜
Hooked you up with some carrots.
兔八哥的那种  我知道你喜欢
Bugs Bunny status, like I know you like.
不知道你收到我短信了没
I, uh, I don't know if you got my text.
这里信号不太好吧  但...
Probably not a great signal in here, but...
你妈要晚点来
your mom might be a little late.
她一定会来的  我知道她超级想见你的
She's coming though 'cause I know she's dying to see you.
算了  我在骗谁呢
All right, man, who am I kidding?
她不会来了
She's not coming.
我知道这很残酷
I know that's hard to hear,
相信我  苦等老妈不出现
and trust me, mothers not showing up,
对我来说是家常便饭
I've been there.
但无论她人在哪里
But, I know wherever she is,
她都会想着你
she is thinking of you.
好吧  这也是假的
Okay, that's not true either.
告诉你件事
Here's the thing.
你妈靠不住
Your mom is a flake.
你有两个选择
And you got two options,
要么坐在这里自怨自艾
you can sit around feeling sorry for yourself
要么自言自语  说"我妈不在
or you can say, "Hey, my mom's not here.
我可以看一整天电视
"I can watch tv all day
然后跑去踹邻居的窗户  只因我心血来潮"
and then go kick in a neighbor's window because I feel like it."
喂
Hey.
喂  看着我
Hey, look at me.
她不来  不是你的错
The fact that she's not here is not your fault.
是她的错
It's hers.
瞧  幸好有我鼓励你
There, I just saved you, like,
你才不会误入歧途  到处乱搞
14 inappropriate sexual encounters.
栗宝
Hi, Chestnut!
宝贝
Hi, baby.
我想你
I missed you.
我好想你哦
I missed you so much.
你有想我吗
Did you miss me?
你最后把蛋糕粉如数拿齐了吗
So you got all the cake mix?
对  还拿到了那23美元
Yes, plus the $23.
我帮你买了贝尔堡的蛋糕粉
And I got you your Pillsbury as well.
全价买的  真要命
Paid full price-- it killed me.
你就是折价券怪胎
You are a freak with the coupons.
我知道
I know.
我也不知道我当时中什么邪了
I don't know what came over me.
我学到了免费得馅饼的方法后
When I found a way to make free money
我就把其他人抛诸脑后了
I forgot about everyone else.
天啊
Oh, my God.
就好比我父亲
Like my father.
麦克斯  我有骗子基因
Max, I have Ponzi DNA.
是啊  折"骗"券基因
Yeah, cou-Ponzi DNA.
从小就得什么都自学很辛苦吧
Must have been hard learning to do everything on your own.
我是说  我也不会做你刚说的每一件事
I mean, I don't know how to do any of that stuff either,
可是  我有20个人伺候我呢
but, I had a staff of 20.
我20的时候还被葡萄球菌伺候过呢
Yeah, I got staph at 20.
你可能觉得你的秘方是
You know, you may think your secret ingredient
一勺贝尔堡
is a spoonful of Pillsbury,
其实不然
but it's not.
是你
It's you.
你所经历的一切
It's everything you've been through
造就了今天的你
that makes you who you are.
会为了一盒卫生棉条
Someone who fights for a box of tampons
或一匹马的感受而奋战
and fights for a horse's feelings
甚至当有朋友深陷折价券不能自拔时
and even fights for a box of cake mix
你甚至还会为了一盒蛋糕粉  代友出征
when a friend in the middle of a cue-Ponzi panic, asks her to.
如果这是生活台的剧  那剧情就是
This is the part in the lifetime movie version
我该起身尿尿了
where I get up to pee.
我不知道你想骗谁
I don't know who you're kidding.
剧情应该是  你看完整部电影  然后你号啕大哭
You watch the entire movie and then you cry.
瞧她那口气  栗宝
Listen to her, Chestnut.
她自以为多了解我
She thinks she has me all figured out.
她不知道其实小蛋糕我还留了一手
What she doesn't know is that when it comes to the cupcakes,
我有个超级秘方
I have another secret, secret ingredient.
别告诉我是少量贝蒂妙厨的蛋糕粉
Oh, don't tell me it's a pinch of Betty Crocker.
我不能说  这可是秘方
I can't tell you. It's a secret ingredient.
好吧  是巧克力味的兴奋剂
Okay, it's chocolate methamphetamine.
不  是真的
No, it's true.
所以我们的口号是
Our slogan should be:
小蛋糕如此美味
They're so good,
让你六亲不认
you'll rob your grandmother.